Welcome back to the Eden channel where
we talk about social media growth
strategies, how to brand yourself in an
irreplaceable way, and just how to stand
out in general from the sea of the same.
Because there are a lot of creators, but
it's never been easier to stand out. And
today, I want to go over how to grow on
LinkedIn because I feel like it is an
underrated platform similar to Substack,
which we went over in another video and
we're going to go over in yet another.
But people sleep on LinkedIn because
it's the corporate platform. It's the
business platform and frankly it's
pretty cringe and corny when you go on
to LinkedIn and I don't really know who
actually scrolls on LinkedIn but maybe
it's the people who are in the jobs
where all they can do is scroll LinkedIn
but if you ask any of the large creators
on LinkedIn and I've talked to quite a
few of them they all say that LinkedIn
is where the money is because on
something like Instagram or even Twitter
there are just a lot of people who are
there to consume and take free
information which there is nothing wrong
with but the people on LinkedIn in are
looking to improve themselves and grow
their businesses and they're willing to
pay for something that gives them an
ROI. So, for those who want to make a
decent amount of money in a short amount
of time, not like a get-rich quick
scheme, just in terms of platform
choice, I would probably go with
LinkedIn. And the interesting thing
about LinkedIn is that there's like only
one style of post that goes viral time
and time again. So, it's a lot easier
than other platforms to create content
for because you know what you're showing
up to create every single day. And the
post formats that tend to go viral look
exactly like this. And you can see how
well these have done, right? 25,000
likes, 48,000 likes. And what's funny
here is that this is a screenshot of a
tweet that got 3,000 likes, but on
LinkedIn, the the screenshot of the
tweet got 25,000 likes. So that's a lot
of people's growth strategy is to quite
literally just repost their tweets and
they tend well not all the time but they
tend to get a good amount of engagement
and sometimes they just do absurdly well
and the reason this type of post works
I've done this on in this is actually
how I grew initially on Instagram and on
LinkedIn is I had already grown on
Twitter meaning that I had quite a few
posts with a decent amount of engagement
and likes and retweets and so I just put
that into a post template like this to
show that the social proof is already
here. So even if I have zero followers,
I still have a lot of engagement on the
post technically and that makes people
pay attention and think that the idea is
good. And so they're more likely to see
me as an authority on LinkedIn even if I
have a very low follower account. And
you can see that like this is all Alex
Hormosi posts. And I'm pretty sure he
cross-osts these to both LinkedIn and
the YouTube community post, not videos
on YouTube, but on the actual post tab
that those tend to get a lot of
engagement on YouTube as well. So if
you're on YouTube, why not post on
LinkedIn and then just crossost it to
your YouTube posts. And now I'm going to
show you how to actually create these
style of posts, but there is a link in
the description for the LinkedIn post
studio. And what this is, think of it
like a custom GPT. It's an AI that you
can chat with that has reference
documents with a bunch of information
related to LinkedIn. And what those
reference documents are are like
breakdowns of viral posts. So this
LinkedIn post studio knows what goes
viral. So you can ask it for ideas. You
can give it your own ideas and it will
help you turn that into a viral LinkedIn
post. Now when I say that these type of
posts go viral, it's not only the posts
with like tweets inside of them. It's
really just any kind of attention
grabbing image. So, if I go to the
discover tab and I just filter by
LinkedIn here. So, turn all of these
off. You can see exactly what I'm
talking about, right? You've got the
tweet style post, you've got an image
here, Gary Vee, you've got Grant Cardone
doing the same thing. Uh, this one went
viral. This one went viral. Like, I
would just encourage you to come and
look through these because you can see
exactly what I'm getting at. And if you
don't want to do the tweet style post,
then what you really need to do, and
I'll show you this in a second after I
show you how to create the tweet style
post, is save a bunch of the formats
that you like to a LinkedIn swipe file
board inside of here so that you create
somewhat of an inspiration board for
when you actually go to create the
images. Now, of course, I have the
productivity and self-improvement
categories checked on, but you can check
on any category or niche that you're
trying to go into. And you can always
just ask the AI chat or connect Claude
to Eden via the MCP and ask it to give
you top performing LinkedIn posts. So,
how do we actually create these types of
posts if you're starting from nothing?
If you have no idea what to do, well, I
actually did this today. I've been
testing it so I know it works. And this
one went today, so it doesn't have that
much, but I've been doing exactly this
for about a week. and my posts have been
doing pretty freaking well compared to
my previous ones, right? I'm on and off
with LinkedIn. If I actually was
consistent on it, I'd have a lot more
followers than 180,000. But my average
post was probably between like 200 and
400 likes. So 715, 1,200, there was a
1,600 one, 600. Like that's a notable
boost in engagement just by including
these types of images. So, I think
that's a a great and kind of easy way to
start because another thing here is you
don't have to use a a picture of your
own tweet or idea. You can use a picture
of someone else's. I know that Tim
Denning does this quite a bit. So, if we
look up Tim Denning and we go to his
LinkedIn, I can assume that his top
liked are going to look almost exactly
like this. Is this one his own? No. See,
it's a a screenshot or a post of someone
else's idea. And this is a great way for
beginners to grow. I'll tell you why
towards the end, cuz we're going to kind
of talk about growth strategies, but
just know that you don't have to have
your own LinkedIn post image. And one
thing worth mentioning here is that
there is a free post image generator.
So, you can paste an X, threads, or
Substack post link here. Doesn't have to
be your own. And it will turn that into
an actual post. a post image that is.
And you can find this at eden.so/tools.
There's also reals transcript
generators, YouTube transcript
generators, etc. They're all right here.
So, I'm going to show you exactly what I
did today to create this type of post.
And it's posted right here. So, I'm
going to take this text and just paste
it in here. And so, this is where I
schedule content. So, what I tend to do
when I'm actually writing posts is I'll
open the discover feed or I'll open one
of my boards or I'll open my library to
see all of the ideas that I've saved or
the highlights that I have from books or
my bookmarks from Twitter or any link
that I've saved so on and so forth. We
actually released the Android app today
if you're interested in that. And in
theuler, I have these platforms turned
on. So, X, LinkedIn, Substack, and
threads because when I'm writing
something like a tweet, it can just go
out to all of those platforms. there's
no need for me to write something
different. But for LinkedIn, like
obviously just having this as the post
wouldn't do too well. So what I can do
instead is click on the LinkedIn
specific post here and then I can make
edits to this one specifically. And what
I'm going to do is I'm going to use
these two icons. This image icon first
will allow me to turn my idea into an
image post like this. So works just like
that. I can change the settings if I
want to. I can change the text if I want
to. So on and so forth. I can change my
name. I like mine in all caps. So I'm
going to change that. And then I can
turn on or off the verified badge. So on
and so forth. And you can see here it's
only adding it to LinkedIn. So I hit add
to post. And now the LinkedIn one is the
only one with the image. So X has it
turned off. So does Substack. So does
threads. But on the LinkedIn one
specifically, what I want to do is I
want to hit this chat button and it's
going to help me turn this idea into a
LinkedIn style caption that is longer
and fits the LinkedIn platform more. And
I'll show you how we can actually learn
how to write those, but I'm just showing
you how I create my own posts right now.
So, I can click this. It's going to open
up an AI chat and it's going to use the
LinkedIn post skill that we have inside
of here. And then it's going to ask me
what angle I want to use because
obviously I don't just want it to
rewrite what I said in the post. I want
it to be something additional to it. So
it's giving me a few. So the three
angles that it sees are the market
reset, the uncomfortable mirror, or the
optimistic pivot. So it just gives me
different angles on the ideas that I can
run with. And so for this, I'm just
going to say do number one. Just you can
read through it on your own idea and do
that. But you will see that it will
output a caption that works very
specifically for LinkedIn. So it gave us
this and I can just copy paste this into
here or I can tell the chat, hey, add it
to the LinkedIn version of this post and
it will populate it for the LinkedIn
version only. But I'm just going to copy
it because I'm old school. Copy. Boom.
Pop it in here. Paste. Now what I like
to do is I just treat this as
inspiration, right? I I hate AI speak. I
don't want people to see AI speak in my
content. And when I read something like
this, I just want to rewrite it all
anyways. So, I just use this as a
starting point because frankly, one, I
don't really care about LinkedIn if I'm
being honest. And my actual idea that I
wrote is right here. So, the caption is
more of just an addition to that. So,
what I would do, and I'm not going to do
it in in this video, but I would read
through this, and I would essentially
delete half of this, rewrite most of it,
and just make sure it gets across my
actual beliefs. I do not like writing
with AI, but I do understand it, and my
opinion has kind of changed. I do think
it is going to be very much a thing in
the future because people will come
around to understanding that it's never
really been about the writing, the thing
that you like. It's been about what you
choose to post. If you choose to post
slop, then you're just showing that you
have low taste and standards. But if the
ideas are actually good and they
represent what you believe and what you
would say and what you would write
anyway, then the person choosing to post
that is just putting a stake in the
ground and saying, "Hey, this is what I
believe." Because that's what you're
doing with the writing anyways. So,
we'll see where that actually goes in
the future because the debate right now
is very heated. But that is essentially
how I create and schedule the LinkedIn
posts, right? Then I can hit schedule up
here. I can choose the time slot. I can
choose which platform it goes to. So on
and so forth and then hit schedule. So
now the question is how do you actually
write these posts as a beginner or how
do you learn to write posts as a
beginner on any platform not just
LinkedIn but LinkedIn rewards a very
specific style of obviously image and
caption. So, what I want you to do is I
want you to create what's called a swipe
file or inspiration board of five posts
that you really like and you could see
yourself emulating. We talked about this
in the Substack video, but creativity or
originality or building an irreplaceable
brand is essentially taking a bunch of
different pieces from the brands or
posts or ideas that you like because
that's what shaped you as a person
anyways and then mashing them together
until your own unique voice emerges from
that. Right? I don't think I'm this
super original person. Most of my ideas
and beliefs and everything else came
from my parents, my teachers, the books
that I really like, the conversations
that I've had that have actually changed
my mind on things. Like I don't
understand the whole originality
argument because if someone else
presents an idea or I read a book and I
see a really good idea and I believe in
that idea, why would I not immediately
adopt that as a part of my head if it
helps me make better decisions and live
a better life? Why would I not replace
an outdated or non-advantageous idea
that's already in my head with a better
idea that eventually crafts a very
unique identity over time as I do that
over and over and pull inspiration from
so many different people. So, enough of
that. Back to the point. What you're
going to do here is just scroll either
through discover or on social media. And
these don't have to be only LinkedIn
posts. But then what you're going to do
is save some of these to a board. So
you're going to click the plus button
here or you use the Chrome extension and
save it inside of here to the board that
you're going to create. Or on mobile you
can be scrolling something like
LinkedIn. Just hit the share button and
then find Eden in the share to list and
then it'll open up a board picker and
you can save it to the board from there.
But what we're going to do is just click
this, click save to board. We're going
to create a new board. We're going to
call it LinkedIn swipe file. And now
that's saved. It's inside of here. And
now I want you to do that five more
times with five different ideas. And I
just want you to make this a habit over
time because this is a habit of top
creators. You research what's working.
You save inspiration. It's just what you
do. It's essentially notetaking and idea
capture for the creator rather than just
trying to save ideas or highlights that
you found in a book, which can be done
perfectly fine inside of the library.
So, I'm going to save a few more and
then I'll show you what we're going to
do. And actually, one tip here, since
you are a beginner, it may be worth
clicking the breakouts uh category here
or filter because what this does is it
shows you creators with under 50,000
followers whose recent post were a 5x
outlier. And an outlier essentially
means how much better did it do than
your typical post. So if a beginner is
breaking out so to say, you know that
they're doing something right when you
don't know that with a celebrity or
someone with a lot of followers because
they could just be getting a lot of
engagement simply because they have a
lot of followers. All right, so I didn't
save five, but I ended up saving four
LinkedIn posts to my LinkedIn swipe
file. And now we're going to do
something that I I love doing this
because it's just so cool and not a lot
of people use AI this way, even though
it's a kind of obvious way of using AI.
But what we're going to do here is click
the chat button in the board so that the
board is pulled into the chat so that it
understands what's in the board and can
take all of these into context. And now
here's what we're going to say. And this
is what I really like doing. So what I
said here is I want you to look through
all the LinkedIn posts on this board and
do a comprehensive breakdown of them.
The hook, the structure, the
psychological tactics, why they work.
Think of it as if you were teaching me
how to write viral LinkedIn posts from
scratch. And that is a very important
line because the best way to use AI in
my opinion is to just treat it as if it
is so stupid. Because most of the time
it is. If I come in here and I say,
"Hey, write me a viral LinkedIn post."
It's just going to pull from its
training data, which is from all over
the internet and from all sorts of
opinions when that's not how content
works. Like Justin Welsh, Chase Diamond,
the people on this board, myself, we all
have our own frameworks and strategies
that we use and there isn't really a way
to just mash those all together into a
general guess of what works well on
LinkedIn and claw, chat, GPT, etc. can't
access social media posts. So, they
can't look at the structure and see what
works. So, I would assume that most of
the time they're just looking at blog
posts or YouTube videos or other things
on how to write LinkedIn posts to string
together just a pretty bad way of
writing a post and it just sounds like
super AI. And so, the reason I like
treating AI as just like this stupid
person or like a base level employee is
because I have to train it. I have to
tell it exactly what to do. When I first
had AI, this was a few years ago, try to
replicate how I write tweets, it just
couldn't do it. But then I wrote like a
2,000word prompt on exactly how I think
about writing tweets. And then it got
super close. It was very close to being
able to write my tweets. And while I
didn't use that to write my tweets, it
was incredible at me being able to give
it my newsletter and then it would pull
out the big ideas and draft those as
tweets. And then I could see my own
ideas then in the tweet form rather than
trying to look through my newsletter and
pull ideas out of it. I could already
see them as like a prototype or a first
draft. And so that's what we're trying
to do here with these LinkedIn posts is
we're trying to create a guide that we
can then give the AI so that it knows
exactly how to create a viral LinkedIn
post. And that's why it's so important
to choose the post that you would want
to emulate personally. So, I'm going to
hit enter on this. All right. So, what
it is doing is it opened the board and
then it opened the post to get
everything inside of the post. And now
it's creating the breakdown for us as a
document inside of our library that we
can then add or organize into a board
that we're going to call our breakdowns
board because it's useful to save these
things because if it works really well,
why wouldn't you save it? And another
fun thing that you could do is just hit
slash and then tab and then you can turn
it into a skill so that you have your
own like LinkedIn writer in the AI chat.
So whenever you go to write a LinkedIn
post, it understands exactly how to
write the LinkedIn post. So, what I
would do is after this is done
generating is hit enter on the skill
creator skill because that helps you
create a skill and then say turn this
breakdown into a skill and then that
will add the skill to your Eden so that
you can access it in a chat later and
this is still going. Yeah, this is
definitely a comprehensive breakdown but
that's exactly what we want. All right,
this is actually getting extremely big
and I'm kind of worried at this point so
maybe don't say comprehensive. All
right, so it finally finished and here's
the full breakdown. We can open this up
and then we can look through this. And
what I would personally recommend is
actually reading through this, right?
Because this is essentially like you
just created your own guide on how to
create LinkedIn posts. And so whenever
you're stuck writing a LinkedIn post,
you can reference this document in a
chat and just ask it, hey, help me to
finish this LinkedIn post. Or you can
just ask the chat questions about it. So
we have all of this broken down. the
psychological tactics for this post,
authority borrowing, complexity
reduction, the iterative reframe, the
openloop CTA, why it worked, post two,
Justin Welsh, so on and so forth. This
was a very long document, so we're not
going to read all of this, but it is
here. So now we can go back to the old
chat here and do what we want to do
next, or let's just create a new chat to
save context and have everything cleared
out. And then we're going to type this
out. So at viral LinkedIn postb
breakdown because that's what we just
created. So what I said is I want you to
interview me to pull content ideas out
of me. Get the necessary information you
need like what I talk about or parts of
my story. Then help me generate
different angles on those ideas. After
that, we're going to use the LinkedIn
post breakdown to turn those ideas into
structured LinkedIn posts that have high
potential of going viral. So you can hit
enter on this. I'll hit enter on this
just so you can see what it says. But
we're not going to go through this
entire process because you can just chat
with it, right? And it works pretty well
and it's based off of data. And the
other thing you can do here at at the
end once you've actually created the
post is again you can type slash and
then go to skills and then hit skill
creator and then say I want to turn this
entire process into a skill that I can
replicate. And then do you see how
powerful that is? Because once you've
gone through this process once,
essentially a skill is like procedural
knowledge. It's kind of like a prompt in
a sense. But then if you have this
entire process saved as a skill, then
when you need to create a LinkedIn post,
you just go to the chat or you go to
Claude if it's connected to the Eden MCP
and then you type slash LinkedIn writer
skill, the one that you create, and then
say, "Help me write LinkedIn posts." And
then it does the exact same thing just
faster. So you can just repeat that over
and over again. So as you can see it
said this what's your domain what's your
story what's your audience what's your
goal etc the other helpful thing here
and the way I want you to think about
using AI is like how can I turn these
into documents that I can reference
easily the next time right because I
have a brand strategy document I have
documents of my past newsletters I have
documents about my story my information
etc it's all inside of my library but if
you don't have that then it would be
wise as you're doing this to answer all
the questions and then say at the end,
hey, create a document in in my library
with all the information I just gave you
about me so I can reference it in
another chat when I need to. And there's
also another video on this channel
called my entire social media strategy
for the next 90 days, something like
that. Now, I talk about my entire
strategy, but one thing that I recommend
doing that I recommend inside of there,
too, is go to the custom AI tab, click
explore, and the very first one,
personal brand strategist. Add this to
your workspace, and then it's going to
open up a chat with all of the
information in here. So, it has a
six-hour video from Caleb Rston on
building a personal brand. It has other
personal branding videos inside of
there. It has playbooks and documents.
And so you're essentially chatting with
all of these things, but what this
strategist does is it gives you a
document with your entire personal brand
strategy, right? And then you can
reference that document over and over
again. It gives you your content
pillars, your audience, your mission,
your vision, your anti-vision, an entire
brand that is much better than really
any brand strategy that you'll come up
with. I recommend this for people who
have been creating for a while as well.
Because even when I went through this, I
was like, "Wow, this is a great
refresher." And now I have something I
can come back to when I need to realign
with what it is that I talk about. So I
would highly highly recommend going
through this before or after you
actually do what I just showed you. Now,
one other thing with this chat is that
you don't always have to ask it to
interview you to pull content ideas out
of you. If you already have an idea that
you want to write about, you can simply
use this breakdown that we created to
help turn that idea into a structured
post. And remember, you could do this
for any content on any platform, not
just LinkedIn. That's just what we're
going over in this video. And so the
question then is like, okay, well, how
do I come up with my own ideas? Well,
you read a book or you have a
conversation or anything like that. And
then you can use the mobile app or you
can just come in here into the library
and then you hit new and you hit card
because that's for a quick idea. And
then you just jot it down really quick
inside of here. And one other thing that
I want to show you is I just filtered
this by Substack to give you an idea,
but there is a reader mode inside of
Eden. So Eden isn't only just for like
creating content because in order to
create good unique content that most
other apps I guess just don't get is
that you need to read, you need to fill
your mind with ideas like Eden is both a
second brain for ideas, but then the
other side of that is it's for creators
to actually turn those ideas into good
content. So, I can paste a link to any
Substack article or I can upload a PDF
or an EPUB or paste a link to an X
article and then I can just go into
these like this one and then I can set
it in my settings to open the reader
view by default if you don't care about
any of this. But then I can just hit the
reader mode and now I can read the
entire article here or on my phone and
then I can highlight ideas and then once
these are highlighted those will save to
my library as well as individual
highlights. And in the library, we
autotag and categorize everything. So
when you search the library either via
the chat or inside of library itself, it
can find anything. So if you say, "Hey,
I want to create a piece of content
around learning and then I want to
structure it into a LinkedIn post. Can
you help me with that?" It will probably
find your highlights on this on learning
and this Substack article and anything
else that you've saved related to
learning and be able to use those ideas
as the ideas for your LinkedIn post. So
now to pivot into more of the growth
side of things like growth on LinkedIn.
Growth on any social media platform is
not only about posting. That's what a
lot of maybe beginners get wrong is they
think that they just post and then the
algorithm just potentially blesses them
and makes them go viral and then they
gain a ton of followers. But that's
that's just not how it works. But it's
understandable because as a beginner,
you don't really treat this as a
business. you treat it as like a hobby
or something that you're going to try
and and see if it works out when that's
a failing strategy. That's not a
strategy. What you have to understand is
that every big creator or every creator
that succeeds has some form of business
sense to them. And they understand that
social media is a traffic mechanism for
their business. And so they have to
treat it as a business. But the creators
who love the artistic and creative side
have to balance that out with the art
and the creative side of it. So, we're
going to go over a few little tips, but
the next creator boot camp for Eden
starts on September 9th, and that's
where we go over everything. We go over
branding, short form content, long- form
content, and then social media growth
and like the depths of social media
growth that most people don't talk
about. And so, you can join the boot
camp with the link in the description,
and that is included on an Eden Pro
annual plan. Or, if you just buy the
boot camp, you can use that as credit
towards an Eden Pro plan as well. if you
don't want to sign up now but want to
sign up later and you get 60 days of
Eden Pro included with the price of the
boot camp. So whether you want the boot
camp standalone, you can do that or if
you want it included with Eden Pro, then
you can do that as well. It's not going
to show that on the landing page, but
just know that what you pay will be a
credit towards your plan if you want it
to be. So if I were to start over and
just go about LinkedIn growth, what I
would do is three things. The first is
just what you do on social media that
everyone is going to tell you you have
to do is you have to reply. Let's say 10
replies a day because social media
growth is less about hoping the
algorithm saves you and is more about
finding unique ways to get your content
in front of other people. And there's
really only one way to get your content
in front of other people without the
algorithm, and that's to put your ideas
in front of other people's audiences
because that's where the followers are,
right? Justin Welsh, myself, other
people have hundreds of thousands of
followers. Those followers might like
your content. And so what you do is you
just time block it. You put it on your
calendar for 30 minutes to go into
LinkedIn to scroll to find a post and
then comment on it. And the way that you
leave a comment really matters because
everyone on LinkedIn and really every
social media platform is just flooding
the replies with very terrible comments
that nobody cares about. Nobody wants to
click on it and follow because like if
you just say, "Oh, this was a great
insight. This was a great post." Who in
their right mind is going to see that
and be like, "Oh, that's someone worth
following. I'm going to click on their
profile and follow them because that was
just super valuable." So, what I would
do is leave a comment worth following.
And what that tends to mean is giving a
tangential idea to the post that you're
commenting on. So you give another
insight. You give value. You give some
actionable steps. You give what worked
for you. Or my favorite is to just say
how the post relates to your life or a
part of your story. So, if someone like
Justin Welsh created a post on work life
balance and how you shouldn't how you
should be slowing down, then I would
think about a time in my life where I
was going too fast and I would write a
paragraph reply on that. And that is so
much more worth following than just
leaving, oh, this was a great post
because you're being lazy and just know
that you have to leave 10 comments today
and treat it as a chore. So, just don't
do that. Leave a quality reply. The next
thing that I would do is what I showed
you earlier with on the image inside of
the post, right? There's the caption and
then there's the image. And for the
image, I would use someone else's idea
that has already gone viral because that
is a proven idea. That means it's much
more likely to get engagement because
it's already gotten engagement before.
So, I would put that in a post style
image with their profile picture, their
name, and then the tweet, the thread,
the Substack note, the LinkedIn post,
whatever it may be. I put it inside of
there. And then I write my own point of
view as the caption, and I tag the
person that I'm including the idea for
in the caption so that they are more
likely to see it. So, let's say Sahil
Bloom as an example. I find one of his
viral posts. I go to Eden. I go to the
creators tab. I filter by top liked. I
find one of his posts that I can give my
own ideas on. I turn that into a post
style image. I put it in theuler or just
upload it to LinkedIn. And then I write
my own caption with a hook, a body,
value. And then I say, "This was an
incredible idea from Sahil Bloom." Sahil
Bloom has like 800,000 followers on
LinkedIn. And the reason this works is
because the creators aren't stupid.
Sahil Bloom knows that if he likes or
comments or shares that post that people
are going to see his idea and follow him
as well. So, it's mutually beneficial.
And what that also means is if I do that
time and time again, I make posting
other people's ideas with my own point
of view as a consistent part of my
content strategy, then I'm increasing my
chances for them to share the actual
post. So, Sahil Bloom, 800,000
followers, he shares the post. That's
way better than getting picked up by the
algorithm. So, that's step two. I would
reply 10 times a day with a good reply
because that's just basic social media
advice and you need to make yourself
known in the community. You just need to
get more eyes on you so people get used
to you. And then two is I would use
other people's ideas with my own point
of view and post that two to three times
a week. And then the third thing that I
would do is just get really good at
writing good content, good ideas. If you
watched the how to grow on Instagram
from zero followers video, you know that
that is what I was harping on over and
over again. The formats, the viral
hooks, the whatever the templates, the
things that you can download, those are
okay, but they don't matter. You have to
focus on the quality of ideas and what
you're putting out every single day. You
just have to get good at the main job of
being a content creator is creating good
content. And so, we went over that
throughout this entire video. So, with
those three things, you're off to an
incredible start with growing on
LinkedIn. So, I will leave it at that.
Again, there is the creator boot camp
link in the description. There's the
LinkedIn post studio link in the
description and a few other things down
there that you can take a look at. But,
I will leave it at that. Thank you for
watching. I hope it was valuable.